<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Atlas NFT</title><link>https://atlasnft.art/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Atlas NFT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atlasnft.art/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Atlas NFT</title><link>https://atlasnft.art/page/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atlasnft.art/page/about/</guid><description>Atlas NFT is a project dedicated to generative art and photography. It&amp;rsquo;s main focus at the moment is The Atlas of Fleeting Moments. There will be serveral drops. Stay tuned for updates.
Use the links below to follow this project also on other channels:
Twitter OpenSea</description></item><item><title>Provenance</title><link>https://atlasnft.art/page/provenance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atlasnft.art/page/provenance/</guid><description>This page contains important information that can be used to track provenance of each NFT released by this project and verify their authenticity.
Verify Authenticity Each NFT from atlas-nft project will be listed on this site along with all the information required to verify their authenticity. These info include:
Contract Address Token ID Metadata To verify you are actually buying NFTs from this project on OpenSea, once you have reached the asset page, go to the details section (see image below) and ensure that:</description></item><item><title>The Atlas of Fleeting Moments</title><link>https://atlasnft.art/page/collection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atlasnft.art/page/collection/</guid><description>The Atlas of Fleeting Moments is a collection of unique collectible moments in the form of 1/1 NFTs on the Polygon blockchain.
Reality is ephemeral, the very fabric of what is eludes true perception and escapes trough our own fingers. The theatre staging the unfolding of this poignant story we called time.
What we are left with is the opportunity to capture fleeting snapshots of our reality like fragile worlds inside tiny glass globes.</description></item></channel></rss>